<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>chmod +x singularity.sh</title><link>http://bt3gl.github.io/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://bt3gl.github.io/feeds/existence.rss.xml" rel="self"></atom:link><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><item><title>Closing an Enormous Cycle</title><link>http://bt3gl.github.io/closing-an-enormous-cycle.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="cyberpunk" height="150" src="./cyberpunk/shrooms.jpg" width="250" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seven years later, I am back to Brazil. Not only the country, the land, the physical. I'm re-encountering an entire new microscosmo that has gigantically developed since I left. Slowly I have been feeling that old nostalgic poetry, and this gives me inspiration for my future selves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My documentary about my dad's extinction and the meaning of life has been too cathartic. I have been having seconds thoughts about producing it every single day since I started it. And this is because I have chosen to live my life as a nihilist, turning any pain in absurdity. But I now can feel that the creative process is healing me, and this is fantastic. In the end I will be stepping up another degree in my artistic journey. I know, it sounds deep, but that's how I have decided seeing it. This project is in post-production and I will talk more about it soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In parallel, I started a project named Humanoids. My idea is to produce short interviews with people around the world, asking them their own meaning of life. We are, above all, the same race of humanoids. More later!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, &lt;a href="https://vimeo.com/193917080"&gt;Scott still haven't given up!&lt;/a&gt;, he is soon facing more challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's clear for me now that I'm ready to go back to San Francisco, the place where I feel and call home. I am excited about this new and magic cycle in my ephemeral history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Love as the best form of activism,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marina&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ps: Found the pictures above during my research. They are photographs of magic mushrooms that my dad took, circa 1989.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Marina von Steinkirch</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>tag:bt3gl.github.io,2016-12-31:closing-an-enormous-cycle.html</guid></item></channel></rss>