<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>chmod +x singularity.sh - web, design</title><link href="http://bt3gl.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://bt3gl.github.io/feeds/web-design.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://bt3gl.github.io/</id><updated>2017-11-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated><entry><title>The Tao of UX/UI Design</title><link href="http://bt3gl.github.io/the-tao-of-uxui-design.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-11-13T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-11-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Marina von Steinkirch</name></author><id>tag:bt3gl.github.io,2017-11-13:/the-tao-of-uxui-design.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="cyberpunk" height="300px" src="./cyberpunk/15.jpg" width="400px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a developer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TALKING TO YOUR TEAM — WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU BUILDING?
In general, the first point of contact a web development team will have with a UX designer or design team is when a new product feature, or even a new product, is proposed for implementation. When this feature …&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="cyberpunk" height="300px" src="./cyberpunk/15.jpg" width="400px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a developer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TALKING TO YOUR TEAM — WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU BUILDING?
In general, the first point of contact a web development team will have with a UX designer or design team is when a new product feature, or even a new product, is proposed for implementation. When this feature has been proposed, perhaps by the CTO of your company, the web development team will come together with the design team to discuss initial ideas for how the project should be approached.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the name ‘designer' a UX designer's role consists of far more than simply creating the physical designs for a product. From the outset of a project, a UX designer is hands-on with research, testing and keeping the team focused on the needs of the user. Despite the fact that UX is more typically associated with ‘design', the actual wireframing and prototyping phases come a lot later on, and are no more important than these earlier stages.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>